let jsonOBJ = {
    "Blue": [
       {
          "Question": "What’s your relationship with Miss White?",
          "Answer": "I am the husband of Miss White and we have been together happily for two years."
       },
       {
          "Question": "What's your relationship with The Monk?",
          "Answer": "I met him a few times and he gave me the potion to use it on Miss White. She turned into a real snake and I got so terrified. Everything went dark for a while. It feels like I was in a dark dark dark abyss. Then I was kidnapped by The Monk and held captive in the tower until my wife, Miss White and Miss Teal came to rescue me."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Is this the snake form you see of Miss White after you give her the potion?",
          "Answer": "Yes"
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen Miss White?",
          "Answer": "A week ago. Before I was kidnapped by The Monk. "
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen The Monk?",
          "Answer": "A day ago. Before I was rescued by Miss White and Miss Teal. I do not think I will still be alive and talking if it weren't for them."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Please describe Miss White’s condition when you last saw her?",
          "Answer": "Honestly, we were having problems since there was so much for me to understand. I am a normal person yet she is something supernatural. But I know she loves me and I really love her. I hope things can work out for the best once this is over."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Did you see or hear what happened during the unnatural flood?",
          "Answer": "I was chained to the tower and left with no food and water for a whole week. I was blindfolded in the dark tower so I couldn't see what really happened when the flooding took place. The wall of the tower was so thick that I could only hear the commotion but wasn’t able to hear any conversations."
       }
    ],
    "White": [
       {
          "Question": "What’s your relationship with Xu xian?",
          "Answer": "I am the wife of Xu xian for two years."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Did you fake that you are a human?",
          "Answer": "Yes"
       },
       {
          "Question": "Why did you fake it?",
          "Answer": "When I was a snake and was almost sold by a merchant, Xu xian saved me and set me free. To return his favor, I took the magical pills and turned into a human so that I can return the favor by marrying Xu Xian."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Do you recognize that exhibit?",
          "Answer": "Yes"
       },
       {
          "Question": "Did you cause the flood? If so, Why did you do it?",
          "Answer": "Yes, I accidentally flooded the whole village. I am so sorry for the catastrophe I created. I regret every second for what I did. But...But! We lived so happily together, and the monk just took my husband away! If I can never see Xu xian again just because I am a snake…I couldn’t help but to save my husband with all my power. How can you force someone to leave their love of the lifetime? (sobbing)"
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen Xu Xian?",
          "Answer": "Three days ago. I snuck to the tower where the monk kidnapped my husband, and saw him blindfolded with no water or food. I got mad and decided to save him out."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Why didn't you save him then?",
          "Answer": "I didn’t think I was able to fight The Monk then and I need to work on my powers and strategize every move possible. Yet, I didn’t think that the flooding would cost so many lives. I am really sorry."
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen The Monk?",
          "Answer": "A day ago. We fought for a whole day until I flooded the village."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Any last words?",
          "Answer": "I am so sorry for the damages I have caused. Before the interference of The Monk, we were just a happily married couple living our plain and simple lives. I appeal you to look at the circumstances I was forced in and decide wisely."
       }
    ],
    "Green": [
       {
          "Question": "What’s your relationship with Miss White?",
          "Answer": "We are sister-like friends. If it weren't for Miss White,I wouldn't become who I am today."
       },
       {
          "Question": "What’s your relationship with The Monk?",
          "Answer": "I do not have direct contact with The Monk. I learned that he was the one to blame for everything that has happened."
       },
       {
          "Question": "What’s your pronoun?",
          "Answer": "I prefer she/her but snake is my original form."
       },
       {
          "Question": "What do you mean by everything that has happened?",
          "Answer": "Miss White was forced to turn into her original snake form from the potion The Monk gave Xu Xian. As a result, Xu Xian was scared to death. She had to get the fairy herb to bring him back to life. I know it is against the rule to bring a normal person back to life. But if you have only known their love and commitment for each other…\nAnd the rest is history. The Monk kidnapped Xu Xian to lure Miss White out. He was killing Miss White. He wanted to capture her and kidnap her for eternity."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Do you recognize that exhibit?",
          "Answer": "Yes "
       },
       {
          "Question": "What do you have to say about this image?",
          "Answer": "I had to help Miss White. I do not want to lose her and I think The Monk is evil. The act of me helping her is purely self defense. You would do so for your best friend if he or she is in danger, wouldn’t you?"
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen Miss White?",
          "Answer": "A day ago after what we did."
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen The Monk?",
          "Answer": "A day ago. Before everything went downward spiral."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Please describe Miss White’s condition when you last saw her?",
          "Answer": "She was in shock. She looked so happy that she got to see Xu Xian again. She also looked so guilty realizing that there were so many innocent creatures getting killed in the way."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Could you describe what happened during the unnatural flood?",
          "Answer": "The Monk was casting some spell on her so that she is paralysed from her power. I couldn’t let that happen so I threw a blunt object towards him to distract him. Miss White got the chance to escape from the spell. She casted the ultimate spell to fight against The Monk and it happened to be the flooding spell."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Any last words?",
          "Answer": "I know we made mistakes. But if the monk didn’t interrupt their marriage, Xu Xian wouldn’t have died and my sister wouldn’t have had to steal the fairy herb. They would have lived happily ever after! It’s all because of him!!!"
       }
    ],
    "Red": [
       {
          "Question": "What’s your relationship with Miss White?",
          "Answer": "Miss White was always ahead of me. She stole the magical pill from me. I was supposed to be the one to take the pill and become a human. Yet it took me 500 years of practice to achieve so. She is the one to blame for the amount of time that could have been saved."
       },
       {
          "Question": "What’s your relationship with Xu Xian?",
          "Answer": "In the past life, Xu Xian was my student and I grew quite protective of him. So in this life, knowing that he and Miss White are together, it is my duty to show him what Miss White truly is."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Do you recognize that exhibit? ",
          "Answer": "Yes "
       },
       {
          "Question": "What do you have to say about this image?",
          "Answer": "I would say it was my point of teaching. One must suffer to realize the mistakes he has made. It was my style of teaching and I always hoped the best for him."
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen Miss White?",
          "Answer": "A day ago after the flooding."
       },
       {
          "Question": "When was the last time you have seen Xu Xian?",
          "Answer": "Two days ago. I was tbh knocked out by the fight and the flooding. All of them were gone before I came to my consciousness."
       },
       {
          "Question": "Please describe Miss White’s condition when you last saw her?",
          "Answer": "She was angry and she was screaming. Oh, there were waves behind her. Then the flood happened, she was lunatic and brutal like a monster! How can a monster trick an innocent human?"
       },
       {
          "Question": "Did you see or hear what happened during the unnatural flood?",
          "Answer": "Yes. "
       },
       {
          "Question": "Could you describe what happened? ",
          "Answer": "I was trying my best to prevent Miss White from being in contact with Xu Xian since what’s best for him is to be a normal person. His life is already complicated enough. There is no need for him to deal with the supernatural incidents in his life. The Miss Teal distracted me with a rock and then last I remembered was the flooding. "
       },
       {
          "Question": "Any last words?",
          "Answer": "Miss White is a thief and a murderer. She stole the magical pill to have the human form. She also stole the fairy herb without permission. What’s more, she murdered all the innocent creatures that are in the village. There are always consequences to one’s actions. I believe Miss White should be punished."
       }
    ]
 }

 export default jsonOBJ;